zozi.com 2014-07-08

# ZOZI

## Privacy Policy

ekoVenture, Inc. ("Company") doing business as (DBA) ZOZI, knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the www.zozi.com and advance.zozi.com websites and domain names, or otherwise accessing any other linked pages, features, content, or services offered from time to time by Company in connection therewith (collectively, the "Website"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

## What does this privacy policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers Company's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Company gathers when you access the Website and when you use Company's services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Company does not own or control, or to individuals that Company does not employ or manage. 

## What personal information does company collect?

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers: 

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US:

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected include your full name, credit card information, email address, zip code, IP address, browser information, username, password, historical purchase data and any other information necessary for us to provide our services. The Personal Information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about new services. 

#### FINANCIAL INFORMATION:

We may have access to certain financial information you provide to us through the Website, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the “Payment Processor”), which may in turn provide us with a secured portion of your financial information in order to complete transactions made through the Website. You acknowledge that the use and storage of your financial information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy. 

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY:

  * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or use our services. Company automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, which may include your IP address, cookie information, web browser, device type, the dates and times you viewed pages, and the page you requested. 
  * Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Website and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Company only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many customers as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our Website or services. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use the Website or services, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Company may also use this usage information to deliver customized third party advertisements and information and to track your entries, submissions, and the status of any promotions or other activities. Again, Company never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 
  * We may also obtain information, including Personal Information, from third parties and sources other than the Website, such as advertisers, or other users who import your email address to their address book. We may also, at your discretion, receive information from third party services that provide a mechanism to expose information you have provided to such third party through use of an application program interface (API), such as Facebook Connect. If we combine or associate information from other sources with Personal Information that we collect through the Website, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

#### E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS:

We may use your email address to contact you for administrative purposes, customer services purposes, promotional purposes, to address intellectual property infringement, rights of privacy, or defamation issues. We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from Company if your computer supports this type of program. Company uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. When you receive e-mail from Company, you can opt out of receiving further e-mails by following the included instructions to unsubscribe. 

#### WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to enhance visitors' experiences, to learn more about their use of the Website and to improve the quality of our services. 
  * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Website's most attractive features. 
  * Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

## Will company share any of the personal information it receives?

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below. 

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: We anticipate that we may become affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses may sell items to you through the Website. In other situations, Company may provide services jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business. In other instances, a third party business may provide website hosting and maintenance services for us, and we may share your Personal Information with them solely to the extent it is necessary for these service providers to complete their contractual obligations with us. 

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Company's agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes. 

Financial Information: As stated above, we may have access to a secured portion of your financial information, which is collected and stored by our Payment Processor. We may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Website. 

Promotional Offers: We may send offers to you on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send an email with your request to [help@zozi.com](mailto:help@zozi.com)

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Company, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Company goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Company may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 

Protection of Company and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

Information You Choose to Share: Any Personal Information you voluntarily choose to include in a publicly accessible area on the Website will be available to other users who access that content. This also applies to information you choose to make available through features that connect to third party services, such as Twitter or Facebook. We may also syndicate content exposed in public areas of the Website to third party services. Once you make your Personal Information available in any of these ways, it may be collected and used by the recipients without restriction. 

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. 

## Conditions of use

If you decide to visit the Company websites, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law. 

## Third party websites; Applications

Company services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Websites. These other websites are not under Company control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Company of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Company websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and Company is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites. 

SPECIFICALLY, THE WEBSITE WILL LINK TO FACEBOOK WEBPAGES AND PROVIDE LINKS TO VARIOUS FACEBOOK APPLICATIONS. COMPANY HAS NO CONTROL OVER FACEBOOK'S PRIVACY PRACTICES OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF THE OWNERS OR OPERATORS OF ANY OF THE APPLICATIONS. 

## Is personal information about me secure?

Your Company account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

Company endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, Company cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

## What personal information can I access?

Company allows you to access certain personal information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. Please see your account settings for your options. 

## What choices do I have?

You may decline to share certain information with us, in which case we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality of the Website. You may change or delete your profile information at any time by accessing your account preferences page through the Website. 

You may request deletion of your Company account by sending an e-mail to [help@zozi.com](mailto:help@zozi.com). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. 

You may opt out of certain email communications during the registration process. However, by registering, you opt in for occasional contests and other promotions managed by the Company through a few internal Company lists. You can choose to opt out of these contests or promotion lists at any time by following the link in any of the emails you may receive. By registering, you also agree to receive the daily experience email for the city/area that you live in. We use your zip code to determine this and you can opt out of this email at any time by following the link in the email you receive. You may also opt out of these communications immediately by updating your profile and account settings under the section entitled "email preference". Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

## Data Security

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. If we learn of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate steps. We may post a notice through the Website if such a breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive a notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at [help@zozi.com](mailto:help@zozi.com). 

## International Visitors to the Website

The Website is hosted in the United States. If you choose to use the Website from other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring Personal Information outside those regions to the United States and by providing such information you consent to that transfer. 

## Changes to this privacy policy

Company may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted. 

## Questions or concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at help@zozi.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. 

Effective Date: November 20, 2012

_ZOZI Headquarters_

535 Pacific Avenue, 4th Floor

San Francisco, CA 94133

1-866-267-3273
